It is Amanda Seals, yours truly, and it is time for us to welcome our headliner of the week.
Everybody give that for James Davis.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you for having me.
How do you feel like being on social media and being like a public figure in that space?
How has it changed like your actual real friendships that exist outside of social media?
I always accepted the fact that I have friends, my good friends.
We don't need to talk as much, but I can send my friends memes, videos and communicate on a social media level that just kind of keeps us in contact.
But we don't we're still going to have our catch up calls. But like I think it also exposes who you are.
So if you're just somebody who is a recluse and doesn't and just doesn't want to talk to people, you can really not talk to people.
And you can and then you can just look at people's profiles and feel like you had interaction and you're you're you're in the world and you really haven't.
You miss your ex, you can really miss your ex on social media, you know, like you can investigate, you can get all the information, you know, for me, I use all communication as a means to get up in person.
If you if you're important to me, the best interaction to me is in person, friend, family, lover, like significant other.
Like I like to hang out. So I'm not a big texter. I like to text to be like text, text, text.
And we're going to link up. Right. You know, like or like a purpose.
Yeah.